jav.guru 2019-11-29

# Privacy Policy ⋆ Jav Guru ⋆ Japanese porn Tube

This document details important information regarding the use and disclosure of user data collected on jav.guru

The security of your Data is very important to jav.guru and as such we take all appropriate steps to limit the risk that it may be lost, damaged or misused.

This site expressly and strictly limits its membership and/or viewing privileges to adults 18 years of age and over or having attained the age of majority in their community. All persons who do not meet its criteria are strictly forbidden from accessing or viewing the contents of this Site. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained the age of majority.

 **DATA COLLECTED**

Personal Information:  
Non-Registered users can watch videos without registering and without any information being collected and processed. However, the visitor’s IP address will be recorded in the event that there is any misappropriation of information and/or content.  
Registered Members: Registration is required for uploading videos, and accessing a number of other features. The following personal information is requested at the time of registration: username (required), and email address (required). Additional personal information, such as year of birth, relationship status and sexual orientation may be added on a voluntary basis after registration, for members interested in identifying and potentially contacting other members meeting specific criteria. All this data with the exception of the email address and IP address becomes publicly accessible information.  
Content Uploaded to the site: Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.  
Cookies: When you visit jav.guru, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser session. jav.guru uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. If you remove your persistent cookie, some of the site’s features may not function properly.  
Log File Information: When you visit jav.guru, our servers may automatically record certain information that your web browser sends such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, platform type, domain names and the date and time of your request.  
Emails: If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.  
USES

Your Personally identifiable information submitted to jav.guru is used to provide to the user the website’s features and special personalized features.

Your chosen username (not your email address) is displayed to other Users alongside the content you upload, including videos, comments, at, the messages you send through the jav.guru private mail, etc. Other Users can contact you through, private messages.

Any videos that you submit to jav.guru may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.

We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent.

We may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of key website changes or for customer service purposes).  
OPT-IN AND USER COMMUNICATION – Subscriber’s expressly and specifically acknowledges and agrees that his email address or other means of communicating with subscriber may be used to send him offers, information or any other commercially oriented emails or other means of communications. More specifically, some offers may be presented to the subscriber via email campaigns or other means of communications with the option to express the subscriber’s preference by either clicking or entering “accept” (alternatively “yes”) or “decline” (alternatively “no”). By selecting or clicking the “accept” or “yes”, the subscriber indicates that the subscriber “OPTS-IN” to that offer and thereby agrees and assents that the subscriber’s personal information, including its email address and data may be used for that matter or disclosed to third-parties.”

OPT-OUT AND USER COMMUNICATION – Subscriber’s expressly and specifically acknowledges and agrees that his email address or other means of communicating with subscriber may be used to send him offers, information or any other commercially oriented emails or other means of communications. More specifically, other offers may be presented to the subscriber via email campaigns or other means of communications with a pre-selected preference or choice. If the subscriber does not deselect the pre-selected preference of choice (i.e. “OPT-OUT” of the offer) then the site may transfer the subscriber’s personal profile information to the third-party service or content provider making the offer. If the subscriber deselects the pre-selected preference then no personal information about the subscriber may be disclosed to any third-party service or content provider.  
We analyze aggregated user traffic information to help streamline our marketing and hosting operations and to improve the quality of the jav.guru user-experience.

 **DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

If under duty to do so jav.guru may release data to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce our Terms Of Service and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of jav.guru or our subscribers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations including the police and governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against fraud or any other kind of illegal activity whether or not identified in the Terms Of Service. It is jav.guru’s policy, whenever possible and legally permissible, to promptly notify you upon an obligation to supply data to any third party.  
Should you deliberately upload any illegal material jav.guru shall forward all available information to all relevant authorities and this without notice.  
– We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

 **SECURITY**

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen a password) which enables you to access certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. jav.guru uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to jav.guru and you do so at your own risk.

 **YOUR RIGHTS**

You are entitled to access and correct your Data by doing so directly on the website or by requesting us to do so via the Contact us section.

Jav.guru is committed to compliance with data protection laws and this policy (Privacy Policy) sets out our personal information gathering and sharing practices for jav.guru (the “Website”, “Platform”) and the services we provide to Advertisers and Publishers (the, “You”, “Your”, etc.). Accordingly, we take commercially reasonable measures to adhere to all industry guidelines and will continue to review and improve our privacy policy and procedures to ensure the safety and protection of consumer information.

This Privacy Statement presents our privacy policy, including our privacy practices. Below is information regarding commitment to protecting the privacy of Internet users. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to provide users with clear and complete notice of the user information we may collect in connection with our Services and on our corporate website.

By submitting your information to us, you agree to the processing set out in this Privacy Policy. Further notices highlighting certain uses we wish to make your personal information together with the ability to opt in or out of selected uses may also be provided to you when we collect personal information from you.

This Website may contain links to other third-party websites. If you follow a link to any of those third party websites, please note that they have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies or processing of your personal information. Please check these policies before you submit any personal information to such third party websites.

jav.guru may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This updated policy is effective from 2018.

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, definitions but not otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meanings given to them in Advertiser and Publisher Agreement as displayed on the Website.

This Privacy Policy is intended to explain our privacy practices and covers the following areas:

1\. What personal information about you we may collect  
2\. How we may use your personal information  
3\. Who we may disclose your personal information to  
4\. How we protect your personal information  
5\. Contacting us & your rights to prevent marketing and to access and update your personal information  
6\. Our Cookies Policy  
7\. How changes to this Privacy Policy and the Cookies Policy will be made  
Information we may collect about you  
We may collect and process the following data about you:  
a) The information you give us. This is information about you that you give us by filling in forms on our Website or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. It includes information you provide when you register to use our Website, subscribes to our services, searches for a product, places an order on our site, or other activities commonly carried out on the Website and when you report a problem with our Website. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, financial and credit card information, personal description and photograph, and any other information.

b) Information we may collect about you. With regard to each of your visits to our Website or Platform we may automatically collect the following information:

technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform, and other information;  
information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL), clickstream to, through and from our Website (including date and time), products you viewed or searched for’, page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), methods used to browse away from the page, any phone number used to call our customer service number, and other information.  
Information we receive from other sources. This is information we receive from you if you use any of the other websites we operate or the other services we provide. We are working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies). We may notify you when we receive information about you from them and the purposes for which we intend to use that information.  
Uses made of your personal information and justification of uses  
We may use your personal information in the ways listed below. Use of personal information under EU data protection laws must be justified under one of a number of legal “grounds” and we are required to set out the ground in respect of each use in this policy. These are the principle grounds that justify Our use of your information:  
a) Consent: where you have consented to our use of your information (you will have been presented with a consent form in relation to any such use and may withdraw your consent by notifying us);

b) Contract performance: where your information is necessary to enter into or perform our contract with you;

d) Legitimate interests: where we use your information to achieve a legitimate interest and our reasons for using it outweigh any prejudice to your data protection rights; and

e) Legal claims: where your information is necessary for us to defend, prosecute or make a claim against you or a third party.

We may use your personal information in the following ways. For each use, we note the grounds we use to justify each use of your personal information:  
a) to onboard you onto the Platform. Where you are a designated contact of an Ad Network, you will create an account by providing the relevant information as specified in paragraph 1.1.(a) above. Where you are a representative of a Publisher, you will create an account by providing the relevant information as specified in paragraph 1.1.(b) above

Use justification: consent, contract performance, legitimate interests (to allow is to onboard you as a user);

b) as part of the on-boarding process described in paragraph 2.1(a) above, where you are a designated contact of a Publisher, we will conduct KYC, AML and other checks to decide whether to onboard you on to the Platform. We may disclose such information to third party credit reference and fraud agencies for the purposes of credit analysis and detecting and preventing fraud and crime – please see paragraph 3.5. below).

Use justification: consent, contract performance, legal obligations, legitimate interests (including to ensure you fall within our acceptable risk profile);

c) to provide you with updates and offers, where you have chosen to receive these (please see the section titled “Marketing” below)

Use justification: consent;

d) to ensure that content from our Website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer

Use justification: consent, contract performance, legitimate interests (to allow us to provide you with the content and services on the Website);

e) to analyze it to develop our products, services, and systems and to understand our users’ requirements

Use justification: legitimate interests (to allow us to improve our services);

f) to notify you about changes to our service

Use justification: contract performance, legitimate interests (to allow us to continuously develop our services).

Use justification: consent (which can be withdrawn at any time – please see paragraph 5.1. below)

We will provide an option to unsubscribe or opt-out of further communication on any electronic marketing communication sent to you or you may opt out by contacting us as set out in paragraph 5.4. below.

Disclosures to third parties and justification of uses  
We may permit selected third parties such as business partners, suppliers, service providers, agents and contractors to use your personal information, for the purposes set out in paragraph 2 above who will be subject to obligations to process such information in compliance with the same safeguards that we deploy.  
Use justification: contract performance, legitimate interests (to enable us to effectively provide our services to you)

We may disclose your personal information to third parties, the court service and/or regulators or law enforcement agencies in connection with proceedings or investigations anywhere in the world where compelled to do so. Where permitted, we will direct any such request to you or notify you before responding unless to do so would prejudice the prevention or detection of a crime.  
Use justification: legal obligation, legal claims, legitimate interests (to cooperate with law enforcement and regulatory authorities);

In the event that we (or a part thereof) are (i) subject to negotiations for the sale of its business or (ii) is sold to a third party or (iii) undergoes a reorganisation, you agree that any of your personal information which We hold may be transferred to that re-organised entity or third party and used for the same purposes as set out in this policy, or for the purpose of analysing any proposed sale or re-organisation. We will ensure that no more of your information is transferred than necessary.  
Use justification: legitimate interests (to allow us to change our business).

Transmission, storage, and security of your personal information  
Security over the internet

No data transmission over the Internet or website can be guaranteed to be secure from intrusion; any transmission is at your own risk. However, we maintain commercially reasonable physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information in accordance with data protection legislative requirements.

All information you provide to us is stored on our or our subcontractors’ secure servers and accessed and used subject to our security policies and standards. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential and for complying with any other security procedures that we notify you of. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.  
In accordance with the recommendations of Payment Card Industry Security Standards Council, customer card details are protected using Transport Layer encryption — TLS 1.2 and application layer with algorithm AES and key length 256 bit.  
Export outside the EEA

Certain countries outside the EEA have been approved by the European Commission as providing essentially equivalent protections to EEA data protection laws and therefore no additional safeguards are required to export personal information to these jurisdictions. If we decide that, staff in those countries which have not had these approvals, will have access to your personal information, we will either ask for your consent to the transfer or transfer it’s subject to European Commission approved contractual terms that impose equivalent data protection obligations directly on the recipient unless we are permitted under applicable data protection law to make such transfers without such formalities.

 **Storage limits**

We will retain your personal information for as long as is necessary for the processing purpose(s) for which it was collected and any other permitted linked purpose (for example certain transaction details and correspondence may be retained until the time limit for claims in respect of the transaction has expired or in order to comply with regulatory requirements regarding the retention of such data). So if the information is used for two purposes we will retain it until the purpose with the latest period expires, but we will stop using it for the purpose with a shorter period one that period expires.  
We restrict access to your personal information to those persons who need to use it for the relevant purpose(s). Our retention periods are based on business needs and your information that is no longer needed is either irreversibly anonymized (and the anonymized information may be retained) or securely destroyed.

 **Your rights & contacting us**

Marketing Purposes  
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. You can exercise the right at any time by contacting us in accordance with Section 5.6.  
Updating information  
We will use reasonable endeavors to ensure that your personal information is accurate. In order to assist us with this, you should notify us of any changes to the personal information that you have provided to us by updating your details on the Platform or by contacting us as set out in paragraph 5.6. below.

Objection  
Unless we have overriding legitimate grounds for personal data processing, you may object to us using your personal data if you feel your fundamental rights and freedoms are impacted. You may also object if we use your personal data for direct marketing purposes (including profiling) or for research or statistical purposes. Please notify your objection to us and we will gladly cease such processing unless we have overriding legitimate grounds.

Erasure  
Please notify us if you no longer wish us to hold your personal data (although in practice it is not possible to provide our Service without holding your personal data). Unless we have reasonable grounds to refuse the erasure, on receipt of such a request we will securely delete the personal data in question within one month. The data may continue to exist in certain backup, but we will take steps to ensure that it will not be accessible.

Please create a support ticket using the support platform in order to delete your personal data.

 **Contacting us**  
JAV.GURU is responsible for and is the “data controller” of your personal information processed by us under this Privacy Policy.  
We can be contacted in relation to your rights or any questions you may have in respect of this Privacy Policy or our processing of your personal information by email jav.guru @ yahoo . com

 **Cookies**

Our Website might use cookies to distinguish you from other users of the Website. This helps us provide you with a good experience when you browse our Website and also allows us to improve our Website. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them, please see our Cookies Policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy and/or Cookies Policy

We may change the content of our website or services without notice, and consequently, our Privacy Policy and/or Cookies Policy may change at any time in the future. We, therefore, encourage you to review it from time to time to stay informed of how we are using personal information.

Website Functionality Cookies  
We make use of cookies to provide you with certain functionality. For example, to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in), or to recognize the platform from which you access the site, and to provide enhanced and more personal features. These cookies are not used to track your browsing on other sites.

Cookies policy does not cover third party websites  
Please note that this cookies policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, the privacy practices of third party websites which may be linked to this Website. These cookies are likely to be analytical/performance cookies or advertising cookies.

Changes to the Cookies Policy  
We may update this cookies policy and we would encourage you to review the policy from time to time to stay informed of how we are using cookies. This cookies policy was last updated in 2018.
